<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>site updates on Daddy Trash</title><link>//localhost:1313/tags/site-updates/</link><description>Recent content in site updates on Daddy Trash</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/site-updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gettting the hang of posting</title><link>//localhost:1313/feed/posts/003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/feed/posts/003/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, the blog is live. I&amp;rsquo;ve created this blog entirely from Hugo and the power of Node.js! Welcome to my blog. I will be using this blog like a database for work I post rather it being lost to platforms over time (which has happened). I will be opening a shop soon that will have my work available to the public. Stay tuned!
Things To Expect In the coming months, I&amp;rsquo;ll have both an official physical copy of Magnum Opus as well as a PDF downloadable version of the book in-shop.</description></item><item><title>Second Post!</title><link>//localhost:1313/feed/posts/002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/feed/posts/002/</guid><description>Slowly Migrating! I am still migrating a lot of files back and forth from the old version of DT and I am hoping to get it all situated soon. I practically learned a new computer language within a week&amp;rsquo;s time, and I&amp;rsquo;m still figuring this syntax out, but MAN I am LOVING it!
I am debating using DISQUS still, or using a stand-alone comments section, but I&amp;rsquo;m a lazy motherfucker. I did the hard work of setting this site up, I think I&amp;rsquo;ll just keep Disqus.</description></item><item><title>First post!</title><link>//localhost:1313/feed/posts/001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//localhost:1313/feed/posts/001/</guid><description>Welcome to my 18+ blog site! A giant reminder that NO minors under any circumstance are allowed anywhere on this site. I&amp;rsquo;m not your parent, and anti-social behavior can be left at the door. Thank you! 💓
To my freaks of nature, welcome!
My website is back better than ever with the help of Hugo Syntax. I won&amp;rsquo;t get into it too deeply, but I had to get away from bloated site platforms like Wordpress.</description></item></channel></rss>